{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 43, 56, 33?\nSymbolic Form: [[43, 56, 33, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 18, 27?\nSymbolic Form: [[18, 27, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 466, 708, 30?\nSymbolic Form: [[466, 708, 30, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:\nFind least common multiple for the following values of  a and  b :a=9 ,  b=15","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":1,"Answer":"x = 45","Source":"Elementary Number Theory","Symbolic Form":"[[9, 15, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 43, 56, 33?\nSymbolic Form: [[43, 56, 33, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 18, 27?\nSymbolic Form: [[18, 27, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 466, 708, 30?\nSymbolic Form: [[466, 708, 30, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:\nCalculate least common multiple for the following values of  a and  b :a=74 , b=111","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":1,"Answer":"x = 222","Source":"Elementary Number Theory","Symbolic Form":"[[74, 111, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 43, 56, 33?\nSymbolic Form: [[43, 56, 33, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 18, 27?\nSymbolic Form: [[18, 27, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 466, 708, 30?\nSymbolic Form: [[466, 708, 30, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:\nfind the least common multiple of given numbers: 8, 10, 15","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":1,"Answer":"x = 120","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[8, 10, 15, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 43, 56, 33?\nSymbolic Form: [[43, 56, 33, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 18, 27?\nSymbolic Form: [[18, 27, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 466, 708, 30?\nSymbolic Form: [[466, 708, 30, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:\nfind the least common multiple of given numbers: 45, 63, 98","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":2,"Answer":"x = 4410","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[45, 63, 98, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 43, 56, 33?\nSymbolic Form: [[43, 56, 33, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 18, 27?\nSymbolic Form: [[18, 27, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:What is the smallest common multiple of 466, 708, 30?\nSymbolic Form: [[466, 708, 30, ilcm]]\n\nQuestion:\nfind the least common multiple of given numbers: 1\/2, 9\/8","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":2,"Answer":"x = 0.5625","Source":"Elementary Algebra","Symbolic Form":"[[1\/2, 9\/8, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"No"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\n\nWord Problem: Omar is planting trees. He has enough trees to plant 6, 7, or 14 trees in each row. What is the least number of trees Omar could have ?\nFind the least common multiple of 6, 7 and 14.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 7, 14, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Two numbers are in the ratio 4 : 7. If the second number is 35, find their least common multiple.\nGiven the second number is 35 and the ratio is 4:7. the first number is 4\/7*35 = 20\nFind the least common multiple of 20 and 35.\nSymbolic Form: [[20, 35, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Six bells commence tolling together and toll at intervals of 2, 4, 6, 8 10 and 12 seconds respectively. In 30 minutes, how many times do they toll together ? (excluding the one at start)\nFind the least common multiple of 2, 4, 6, 8, 10 and 12.\nSymbolic Form: [[2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A farmer has 10 cows, 15 sheep, and 20 chickens. He wants to put the animals into pens so that each pen has the same number of each kind of animal. What is the least number of animals that can be in each pen?\nFind the least common multiple of 10, 15 and 20.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 15, 20, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A train to Los Angeles leaves a station every 10 minutes. Another train to San Francisco leaves the same station every 8 minutes. If it is 9:00 am right now, at what time will both trains leave the station together?\nFind the least common multiple of 10 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: At a summer camp, the arts and crafts instructor wants to organize a schedule for the pottery and woodworking classes. The pottery class meets every 6 days, and the woodworking class meets every 8 days. If both classes were last held on the same day, after how many days will they next meet on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 6 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:A bakery makes blueberry muffins every 3 days, and another bakery makes blueberry muffins every 4 days. If both bakeries started making blueberry muffins on the same day, how many times in 24 days will they both make blueberry muffins on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 3 and 4.\nSymbolic Form: [[3, 4, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:\nToday, both the soccer team and the basketball team had games. The soccer team plays every 3 days and the basketball team plays every 5 days. When will both teams have games on the same day again?","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":3,"Answer":"15","Source":"Elementary Number Theory","Symbolic Form":"[[3, 5, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\n\nWord Problem: Omar is planting trees. He has enough trees to plant 6, 7, or 14 trees in each row. What is the least number of trees Omar could have ?\nFind the least common multiple of 6, 7 and 14.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 7, 14, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Two numbers are in the ratio 4 : 7. If the second number is 35, find their least common multiple.\nGiven the second number is 35 and the ratio is 4:7. the first number is 4\/7*35 = 20\nFind the least common multiple of 20 and 35.\nSymbolic Form: [[20, 35, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Six bells commence tolling together and toll at intervals of 2, 4, 6, 8 10 and 12 seconds respectively. In 30 minutes, how many times do they toll together ? (excluding the one at start)\nFind the least common multiple of 2, 4, 6, 8, 10 and 12.\nSymbolic Form: [[2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A farmer has 10 cows, 15 sheep, and 20 chickens. He wants to put the animals into pens so that each pen has the same number of each kind of animal. What is the least number of animals that can be in each pen?\nFind the least common multiple of 10, 15 and 20.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 15, 20, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A train to Los Angeles leaves a station every 10 minutes. Another train to San Francisco leaves the same station every 8 minutes. If it is 9:00 am right now, at what time will both trains leave the station together?\nFind the least common multiple of 10 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: At a summer camp, the arts and crafts instructor wants to organize a schedule for the pottery and woodworking classes. The pottery class meets every 6 days, and the woodworking class meets every 8 days. If both classes were last held on the same day, after how many days will they next meet on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 6 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:A bakery makes blueberry muffins every 3 days, and another bakery makes blueberry muffins every 4 days. If both bakeries started making blueberry muffins on the same day, how many times in 24 days will they both make blueberry muffins on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 3 and 4.\nSymbolic Form: [[3, 4, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:\nBoxes that are 12 inches tall are being piled next to boxes that are 10 inches tall. What is the least height in feet at which the two piles will be the same height?","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":3,"Answer":"60","Source":"Elementary Number Theory","Symbolic Form":"[[12, 10, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\n\nWord Problem: Omar is planting trees. He has enough trees to plant 6, 7, or 14 trees in each row. What is the least number of trees Omar could have ?\nFind the least common multiple of 6, 7 and 14.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 7, 14, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Two numbers are in the ratio 4 : 7. If the second number is 35, find their least common multiple.\nGiven the second number is 35 and the ratio is 4:7. the first number is 4\/7*35 = 20\nFind the least common multiple of 20 and 35.\nSymbolic Form: [[20, 35, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Six bells commence tolling together and toll at intervals of 2, 4, 6, 8 10 and 12 seconds respectively. In 30 minutes, how many times do they toll together ? (excluding the one at start)\nFind the least common multiple of 2, 4, 6, 8, 10 and 12.\nSymbolic Form: [[2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A farmer has 10 cows, 15 sheep, and 20 chickens. He wants to put the animals into pens so that each pen has the same number of each kind of animal. What is the least number of animals that can be in each pen?\nFind the least common multiple of 10, 15 and 20.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 15, 20, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A train to Los Angeles leaves a station every 10 minutes. Another train to San Francisco leaves the same station every 8 minutes. If it is 9:00 am right now, at what time will both trains leave the station together?\nFind the least common multiple of 10 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: At a summer camp, the arts and crafts instructor wants to organize a schedule for the pottery and woodworking classes. The pottery class meets every 6 days, and the woodworking class meets every 8 days. If both classes were last held on the same day, after how many days will they next meet on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 6 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:A bakery makes blueberry muffins every 3 days, and another bakery makes blueberry muffins every 4 days. If both bakeries started making blueberry muffins on the same day, how many times in 24 days will they both make blueberry muffins on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 3 and 4.\nSymbolic Form: [[3, 4, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:\nA man smiles at his beautiful wife every 3 seconds while the wife smiles back at him every 6 seconds. When will both husband and wife smile at each other at the same time?","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":3,"Answer":"18","Source":"Elementary Number Theory","Symbolic Form":"[[3, 6, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\n\nWord Problem: Omar is planting trees. He has enough trees to plant 6, 7, or 14 trees in each row. What is the least number of trees Omar could have ?\nFind the least common multiple of 6, 7 and 14.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 7, 14, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Two numbers are in the ratio 4 : 7. If the second number is 35, find their least common multiple.\nGiven the second number is 35 and the ratio is 4:7. the first number is 4\/7*35 = 20\nFind the least common multiple of 20 and 35.\nSymbolic Form: [[20, 35, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Six bells commence tolling together and toll at intervals of 2, 4, 6, 8 10 and 12 seconds respectively. In 30 minutes, how many times do they toll together ? (excluding the one at start)\nFind the least common multiple of 2, 4, 6, 8, 10 and 12.\nSymbolic Form: [[2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A farmer has 10 cows, 15 sheep, and 20 chickens. He wants to put the animals into pens so that each pen has the same number of each kind of animal. What is the least number of animals that can be in each pen?\nFind the least common multiple of 10, 15 and 20.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 15, 20, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A train to Los Angeles leaves a station every 10 minutes. Another train to San Francisco leaves the same station every 8 minutes. If it is 9:00 am right now, at what time will both trains leave the station together?\nFind the least common multiple of 10 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: At a summer camp, the arts and crafts instructor wants to organize a schedule for the pottery and woodworking classes. The pottery class meets every 6 days, and the woodworking class meets every 8 days. If both classes were last held on the same day, after how many days will they next meet on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 6 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:A bakery makes blueberry muffins every 3 days, and another bakery makes blueberry muffins every 4 days. If both bakeries started making blueberry muffins on the same day, how many times in 24 days will they both make blueberry muffins on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 3 and 4.\nSymbolic Form: [[3, 4, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:\nSteve can save 9 dollars every day while Maria can save 12 dollars every day. What is the least number of days it will take each person to save the same amount of money?","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":3,"Answer":"36","Source":"Elementary Number Theory","Symbolic Form":"[[9,12,ilcm]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
{"Question":"Task: Rewrite the following word problems into Symbolic Form trying to do like the given example.\n\nWord Problem: Omar is planting trees. He has enough trees to plant 6, 7, or 14 trees in each row. What is the least number of trees Omar could have ?\nFind the least common multiple of 6, 7 and 14.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 7, 14, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Two numbers are in the ratio 4 : 7. If the second number is 35, find their least common multiple.\nGiven the second number is 35 and the ratio is 4:7. the first number is 4\/7*35 = 20\nFind the least common multiple of 20 and 35.\nSymbolic Form: [[20, 35, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: Six bells commence tolling together and toll at intervals of 2, 4, 6, 8 10 and 12 seconds respectively. In 30 minutes, how many times do they toll together ? (excluding the one at start)\nFind the least common multiple of 2, 4, 6, 8, 10 and 12.\nSymbolic Form: [[2, 4, 6, 8, 10, 12, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A farmer has 10 cows, 15 sheep, and 20 chickens. He wants to put the animals into pens so that each pen has the same number of each kind of animal. What is the least number of animals that can be in each pen?\nFind the least common multiple of 10, 15 and 20.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 15, 20, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: A train to Los Angeles leaves a station every 10 minutes. Another train to San Francisco leaves the same station every 8 minutes. If it is 9:00 am right now, at what time will both trains leave the station together?\nFind the least common multiple of 10 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[10, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem: At a summer camp, the arts and crafts instructor wants to organize a schedule for the pottery and woodworking classes. The pottery class meets every 6 days, and the woodworking class meets every 8 days. If both classes were last held on the same day, after how many days will they next meet on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 6 and 8.\nSymbolic Form: [[6, 8, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:A bakery makes blueberry muffins every 3 days, and another bakery makes blueberry muffins every 4 days. If both bakeries started making blueberry muffins on the same day, how many times in 24 days will they both make blueberry muffins on the same day?\nFind the least common multiple of 3 and 4.\nSymbolic Form: [[3, 4, ilcm]]\n\nWord Problem:\nTwo men running a marathon took a sip of water at the same time 72 minutes after they started the race. If the first man took a sip of water every 9 minutes, how often did the other man take a sip of water?","Type":"Least Common Multiple","Level":3,"Answer":"72","Source":"Elementary Number Theory","Symbolic Form":"[[72, 9, ilcm]]","Word Problem":"Yes"}
